<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Upvado - Software Solutions on Upvado Software Solutions</title><link>https://upvado.com/</link><description>Recent content in Upvado - Software Solutions on Upvado Software Solutions</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://upvado.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>License Agreement</title><link>https://upvado.com/license-agreement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://upvado.com/license-agreement/</guid><description>&lt;p>This Software License Agreement (&amp;ldquo;Agreement&amp;rdquo;) is a legal agreement between the purchaser (&amp;ldquo;Licensee&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Customer&amp;rdquo;) and &lt;strong>Upvado Software Solutions&lt;/strong> (&amp;ldquo;Licensor&amp;rdquo;) for the use of Upvado Extensions (&amp;ldquo;Software&amp;rdquo;). By purchasing, downloading, installing, or using any Upvado extension, the Licensee agrees to the following terms:&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="1-definitions">1. Definitions&lt;/h2>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>&amp;ldquo;Software&amp;rdquo; refers to any and all Upvado extensions, including all their components, source code, and documentation.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>&amp;ldquo;Licensee&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Customer&amp;rdquo; refers to the individual or entity purchasing, downloading, installing, or using the Software.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>https://upvado.com/privacy-policy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://upvado.com/privacy-policy/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;strong>Effective Date: February 26, 2025&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="1-introduction">1. Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>We value your privacy and are committed to protecting your personal data. This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, disclose, and safeguard your information when you use our website and our products, including our eCommerce extensions for platforms such as Magento, Shopify, and others. By accessing or using our website or products, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="2-information-we-collect">2. Information We Collect&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>We may collect personal data such as your name, email address, company information, and other details you provide when you interact with our website, subscribe to our newsletter, or purchase our products. We also collect non-personal information like browser type, operating system, and pages visited through the use of cookies and similar technologies.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>